{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4850","name":"SS Peter and Paul Jesuit Church","address":"438 St Antoine","zipcode":"48226","owner":"Saints Peter and Paul Jesuit","licenseNumber":"208172","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"5/4/2018","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","geom":"0101000020E6100000C0AA655E73C254C098A5DA6A802A4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"42464","establishmentid":"4850","name":"SS Peter and Paul Jesuit Church","inspectionDate":"2018-06-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Preopening/Other","inspectorid":"122","pcount":"1","pfcount":"1","ccount":"3","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"3","correctedcritical":"2","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"42464","inspectionDate":"6/8/2018","inspectionType":"Preopening/Other","establishmentid":"4850","name":"SS Peter and Paul Jesuit Church","violationCode":"6-201.13","violationDescription":"(A) In FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which cleaning methods other than water flushing are used for cleaning floors, the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and closed to no larger than one thirty-second inch.\r\n(B) The floors in FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which water flush cleaning methods are used shall be provided with drains and be graded to drain, and the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and SEALED.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not coved","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Floor coving","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide / install coved molding."},{"inspectionid":"42464","inspectionDate":"6/8/2018","inspectionType":"Preopening/Other","establishmentid":"4850","name":"SS Peter and Paul Jesuit Church","violationCode":"5-402.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a direct connection may not exist between the SEWAGE system and a drain originating from EQUIPMENT in which FOOD, portable EQUIPMENT, or UTENSILS are placed. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Backflow/backsiphonage prevention device(s)","subItem":"Air gap","problemDescription":"Not provided on","subProblem":"Sink","location":"PREP SINK","subLocation":"On the Drain line","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate air gap."},{"inspectionid":"42464","inspectionDate":"6/8/2018","inspectionType":"Preopening/Other","establishmentid":"4850","name":"SS Peter and Paul Jesuit Church","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"BEVERAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair"},{"inspectionid":"42464","inspectionDate":"6/8/2018","inspectionType":"Preopening/Other","establishmentid":"4850","name":"SS Peter and Paul Jesuit Church","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"BEVERAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"42464","inspectionDate":"6/8/2018","inspectionType":"Preopening/Other","establishmentid":"4850","name":"SS Peter and Paul Jesuit Church","violationCode":"5-103.12","violationDescription":"Water under pressure shall be provided to all fixtures, EQUIPMENT, and nonFOOD EQUIPMENT that are required to use water unless otherwise approved. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Water under pressure","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Insufficient to meet demands","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide sufficient water pressure to meet demand of use."}]},{"inspectionid":"41517","establishmentid":"4850","name":"SS Peter and Paul Jesuit Church","inspectionDate":"2018-02-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"79","pcount":"4","pfcount":"2","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"6","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"5","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"41517","inspectionDate":"2/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4850","name":"SS Peter and Paul Jesuit Church","violationCode":"7-102.11","violationDescription":"Working containers used for storing POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIALS such as cleaners and SANITIZERS taken from bulk supplies shall be clearly and individually identified with the common name of the material. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Working containers-toxics","subItem":"sanitizer","problemDescription":"Not labeled as to content","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"In the Janitor Closet","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-02-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."},{"inspectionid":"41517","inspectionDate":"2/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4850","name":"SS Peter and Paul Jesuit Church","violationCode":"7-204.11","violationDescription":"Chemical SANITIZERS and other chemical antimicrobials applied to FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall meet the requirements specified in this code. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not comply with law","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"In the Janitor Closet","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-02-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove and replace to be in compliance with law."},{"inspectionid":"41517","inspectionDate":"2/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4850","name":"SS Peter and Paul Jesuit Church","violationCode":"4-501.114","violationDescription":"A chemical SANITIZER used in a SANITIZING solution for a manual or\r\nmechanical operation shall meet these limits or as otherwise approved: (P)\r\n\tChlorine        ppm           pH<10             pH<8\r\n\t\t      25              120 F              120 F\r\n\t\t      50              100 F              75 F\r\n\t\t     100              55 F               55 F\r\n                 Iodine           a concentration of between 12.5 and 25 ppm and minimum temp of 75 F and pH of 5 or less or meets manufacturer's specifications. (P)\r\n\r\n                Quats            minimum temperature of 75 F, hardness of 500 ppm or less and meet manufacturers use directions. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Quaternary ammonia solution","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not immersed in","subProblem":"A concentration specified on manufacturers label","location":"WARE WASHING AREA","subLocation":"In the Three compartment sink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-02-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"inspectionid":"41517","inspectionDate":"2/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4850","name":"SS Peter and Paul Jesuit Church","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"SERVING LINE","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"inspectionid":"41517","inspectionDate":"2/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4850","name":"SS Peter and Paul Jesuit Church","violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"In the Refrigerator","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-02-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Establishment shall provide a clear date marking system."},{"inspectionid":"41517","inspectionDate":"2/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4850","name":"SS Peter and Paul Jesuit Church","violationCode":"5-402.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a direct connection may not exist between the SEWAGE system and a drain originating from EQUIPMENT in which FOOD, portable EQUIPMENT, or UTENSILS are placed. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Backflow/backsiphonage prevention device(s)","subItem":"Air gap","problemDescription":"Not provided on","subProblem":"Sink","location":"PREP SINK","subLocation":"On the Drain line","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate air gap."}]},{"inspectionid":"40492","establishmentid":"4850","name":"SS Peter and Paul Jesuit Church","inspectionDate":"2017-10-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"129","pcount":"2","pfcount":"1","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"3","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"3","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"40492","inspectionDate":"10/18/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4850","name":"SS Peter and Paul Jesuit Church","violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Raw animal food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/next to","subProblem":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"At the RAW FOOD STORAGE","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store raw animal foods below and away from foods needing little or no further prep."},{"inspectionid":"40492","inspectionDate":"10/18/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4850","name":"SS Peter and Paul Jesuit Church","violationCode":"3-501.18","violationDescription":"A FOOD specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A) or (B) shall be discarded if it:  \r\n    (1) Exceeds the temperature and time combination specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A),              except time that the product is frozen; (P)\r\n    (2) Is in a container or PACKAGE that does not bear a date or day; (P) or\r\n    (3) Is appropriately marked with a date or day that exceeds a temperature and              time combination as specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A). (P)  \r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Ready to eat, potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Beyond consume by date","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"At the Past date food","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"inspectionid":"40492","inspectionDate":"10/18/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4850","name":"SS Peter and Paul Jesuit Church","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"SANITIZER","subLocation":"At the Test strips","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"}]},{"inspectionid":"36519","establishmentid":"4850","name":"SS Peter and Paul Jesuit Church","inspectionDate":"2016-09-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"121","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4850"}}